A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.39 (A2014) FA760
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.39 (A2014)
1993-2014
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA760
73.51 Cubic Feet 55 standard record storage boxes, R4389-R4442, 1 letter document box, one flat file folder and 1 35mm clamshell box
54 standard record storage boxes, R4389-R4442
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Project files transferred to the RAC by Rockefeller Foundation, 2014.
Arrangement
Records are primarily arranged by Program.
Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
Conditions Governing Access
Records 10 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Separated Materials
Special Formats (audio, film, video, digital media, library materials, memorabilia, oversize, and photographic material) have been separated from the body of the collection. All pertinent items are assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
Other Finding Aids
For other RF project files, please refer to the following findng aids:
FA386 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.1
FA387 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.2
FA388 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.3
FA209 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.3-1.8
FA479 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.9-1.15
FA469 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.16-1.19
FA471 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.20-1.23
FA477 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.25
FA473 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.39
FA761 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.41
Scope and Contents
Grant admininstration files and related material.
- AC.2014.003: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 2001-2014; AC_2014_003; 31.44 Cubic Feet 24 standard record storage boxes, R4389-R4412
  - OAS, 2009-2013; AC_2014_003_1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2009 OAS 301 - WOMEN'S HEALTH AND REPRODUCTIVE RIGHTS FOUNDATION OF THAILAND - "FIRST INTERNATIONAL CONGRESS ON WOMENS HEALTH AND UNSAFE ABORTIONS", 2009-2010 (Box R4389)
    - 2010 OAS 301 - THAI BREASTFEEDING CENTER POPULATION - THAI BREESFEEDING ATLAS, 2010-2012 (Box R4405)
    - 2010 OAS 302 - OXFAM (UNITED KINGDOM) - PROJECT TO PROMOTE CLIMATE CHANGE JUSTICE AND OWNERSHIP CONFLICTS IN THAILAND, 2010-2013 (Box R4405)
    - 2010 OAS 303 - CHULALONGKORN UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - URBAN REVITALIZATION THROUGH ARTS, 2010-2013 (Box R4405)
    - 2010 OAS 304 - CHULALONGKORN UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - INEQUALITY LECTURE SERIES, 2010-2012 (Box R4405)
    - 2010 OAS304 - ISBN: 978-616-551-583-2 - Published Material, 2010-2012; 2014:003:064 (Box R4405)
      Separated Materials
      Special format items (audio, film, video, digital media, library materials, memorabilia, oversize, and photographic material) have been separated from the file and assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
    - 2010 OAS 305 - ARSOM SILP INSTITUTE OF THE ARTS (THAILAND) - PRESERVATION OF LOCAL NEIGHBORHOOD ARCHITECTURE IN SEVERAL SITES, 2010-2013 (Box R4405)
    - 2010 OAS 306 - BRAC UNIVERSITY (BANGLADESH) - TRANSCENDING BINARIES CONFERENCE, 2010-2011 (Box R4405)
    - 2010 OAS 307 - NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF DEVELOPMENT ADMINISTRATION - INTERNATIONAL ANTI-CORRUPTION CONFERENCE, 2010-2011 (Box R4405)
  - Search (SRC), 2004-2013; AC_2014_003_2; 9.2 Cubic Feet 7 record storage boxes
    - 2009 SRC 104 - AFRICAN POPULATION AND HEALTH RESEARCH CENTRE KENYA - URBAN HEALTH IN NAIROBI, 2008-2010 (Box R4389)
    - 2009 SRC 105 - POPULATION COUNCIL - URBAN HEALTH, 2008-2012 (Box R4389)
    - 2009 SRC 108 - TASK FORCE FOR CHILD SURVIVAL AND DEVELOPMENT - URBAN HEALTH, 2008-2010 (Box R4389)
    - 2009 SRC 110 - KENYA INSTITUTE FOR PUBLICH POLICY RESEARCH AND ANALYSIS - NAIROBI METROPOLITAN 2030 PLAN, 2008-2013 (Box R4389)
    - 2009 SRC 111 - PRINCE'S FOUNDATION FOR THE BUILT ENVIRONMENT (ENGLAND) - DEVELOPING PERFORMANCE INDICATORS (Box R4389)
    - 2009 SRC 113 - UNIVERSITY COLLEGE LONDON, UNIVERSITY OF LONDON (ENGLAND) - URBAN HEALTH IN LOW AND MIDDLE INCOME COUNTRIES, 2008-2011 (Box R4389)
    - 2009 SRC 115 - STRATHMORE UNIVERSITY (KENYA) - DATABASE OF CIVIL SOCIETY ORGANIZATIONS WORKING ON URBAN ISSUES, 2009-2010 (Box R4389)
    - 2009 SRC 117 - COMMUNITY ORGANIZATIONS RESOURCE CENTRE (SOUTH AFRICA) - URBAN COMMUNITY PARTICIPATION IN CIVIL SOCIETY, 2008-2011 (Box R4389)
    - 2009 SRC 118 - UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA - DEBATE ON TRANSPORTATION, 2009-2010 (Box R4389)
    - 2009 SRC 119 - SOCIETY FOR PROMOTION OF AREA RESOURCE CENTERS (INDIA) - URBAN HEALTH FINANCING, 2008-2011 (Box R4389)
    - 2009 SRC 120 - AITEX CONFERENCES (ENGLAND) - FORUM FOR KENYA-BASED NGO'S AND KENYAN BPO PROVIDERS, 2009-2010 (Box R4389)
    - 2009 SRC 121 - COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY - URBAN DEVELOPMENT IN NAIROBI, 2008-2011 (Box R4389)
    - 2009 SRC 124 - JAMII BORA CHARITABLE TRUST (KENYA) - INCREASE EFFECTIVENESS IN HELPING THE URBAN POOR, 2008-2012 (Box R4389)
    - 2009 SRC 125 - CONSERVATION LAW FOUNDATION - TRANSPORTATION ADVOCCY IN NEW ENGLAND, 2009-2010 (Box R4389)
    - 2009 SRC 126 - RUTGERS UNIVERSITY - URBAN DEVELOPMENT IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 2008-2012 (Box R4389)
    - 2009 SRC 127 - LIVABLE STREETS TRANSPORTATION ALLIANCE OF BOSTON - ADVOCACY FOR INNOVATIONS IN TRANSPORTATION, 2009-2010 (Box R4389)
    - 2009 SRC 128 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA, IRVINE - CONFERENCE ON THE U.S. HOUSING MARKET, 2009-2010 (Box R4389)
    - 2009 SRC 129 - NETHOPE -SHARED SERVICES FOR INTERNATIONAL DEVELOPMENT, 2008-2010 (Box R4390)
    - 2009 SRC 130 - AYALA FOUNDATION - SUSTANABLE TRANSPORATION AND URBAN DEVELOPMENT IN PHILIPPINE CITIES, 2009-2010 (Box R4390)
    - 2009 SRC 131 - RECONNECTING AMERICA, INC. - CELL PHONE-BASED BUS TRACKING SYSTEMS (Box R4390)
    - 2009 SRC 132 - NEW YORK ACADEMY OF MEDICINE - ROUNDTABLE ON URBAN LIVING ENVIRONMENT RESEARCH, 2009-2011 (Box R4390)
    - 2009 SRC 135 - MERIDIAN INSTITUTE - CONVENING AND ANALYSIS FOR U.S. NATIONAL SMART POWER GRID, 2009-2010 (Box R4390)
    - 2009 SRC 136 - ACADEMY FOR EDUCATIONAL DEVELOPMENT - OUTSOURCED MONITORING ND EVALUATION TOOL FOR KENYAN NGOS, 2009-2012 (Box R4390)
    - 2009 SRC 137 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR LIVING AQUATIC RESOURCES MANAGEMENT (MALAYSIA) - SHARED SERVICE OPERATING MODEL OF CGIAR, 2009-2010 (Box R4390)
    - 2009 SRC 138 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA, DAVIS - STATE-WIDE TRAVEL MODEL LINKING TRANSPORTATION AND LAND USE, 2009-2011 (Box R4390)
    - 2009 SRC 139 - TRANSFORMCA - GREENTIP: TRAFFIC REDUCTION AND INNOVATIVE PARKING PROGRAM, 2009-2011 (Box R4390)
    - 2009 SRC 140 - SAMASOURCE - JOBS CREATION FOR WOMEN AND YOUTH IN DADAAB REFUGEE CAMPS OF KENYA, 2009-2012 (Box R4390)
    - 2009 SRC 141 - GSMA FOUNDATION - HELPLINE FOR KENYAN SMALLHOLDER FARMERS, 2009-2012 (Box R4390)
    - 2009 SRC 142 - URBAN INSTITUTE - ASSIST HUD ON HOUSING AND URBAN DEVELOPMENT ISSUES, 2009-2011 (Box R4390)
    - 2009 SRC 144 - NEXT AMERICAN CITY - CONFERENCE, OPEN CITIES - NEW MEDIA'S ROLE IN SHAPING URBAN POLICY, 2009-2012 (Box R4390)
    - 2009 SRC 148 - SMART GROWTH AMERICA - STATE ADVOCAY CAMPAIGN ON TRANSPORTATION, 2009-2010 (Box R4390)
    - 2009 SRC 150 - HABITAT FOR HUMANITY INTERNATIONAL - WORLD HABITAT DAY 2009 RELATED ACTIVITIES, 2009-2011 (Box R4391)
    - 2009 SRC150 - World Habitat Day 2009 Opening Ceremony Clips Disk 1-2 - Digital, 2009-2011; 2014:003:009, 2014:003:010 (Box R4391)
    - 2009 SRC150 - World Habitat Day 2009 Dinner Clips - Digital, 2009-2011; 2014:003:011 (Box R4391)
    - 2009 SRC150 - WHDay 2009 evening clips - digital, 2009-2011; 2014:003:012 (Box R4391)
    - 2009 SRC 151 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - "HISTORY LESSONS FOR TODAY'S HOUSING POLICY", 2009-2010 (Box R4391)
    - 2009 SRC 152 - LOCAL GOVERNMENT COMMISSION - 9TH ANNUAL NEW PARTNERS FOR SMART GROWTH CONFERENCE, 2009-2010 (Box R4391)
    - 2009 SRC 153 - INITIATIVE FOR A COMPETITIVE CITY - INNER CITY ECONOMIC STAGNATION PROJECT, 2009-2011 (Box R4391)
    - 2009 SRC 154 - FRONT SEAT MANAGEMENT, LLC - WALK SCORE SYSTEM, 2009-2010 (Box R4391)
    - 2009 SRC 156 - CHF INTERNATIONAL - CONVENINGS AS PART OF PREPARATIONS FOR THE WORLD URBAN FORUM, 2009-2011 (Box R4391)
    - 2009 SRC 157 - LIVING CITIES, INC. - TRANSPORTATION ORIENTED DEVELOPMENT MODEL; EQUITABLE URBAN DEVELOPMENT, 2009-2010 (Box R4391)
    - 2009 SRC 158 - NATIONAL GOVERNORS ASSOCIATION CENTER FOR BEST PRACTICES - TECHNICAL ASSISTANCE TO U.S. GOVERNORS, 2009-2012 (Box R4391)
    - 2009 SRC 159 - DECENTRALISED ENERGY SYSTEMS INDIA PRIVATE LIMITED (INDIA) - MOBILE PHONE TOWERS, 2009-2011 (Box R4391)
    - 2009 SRC 160 - GREATER OHIO POLICY CENTER - FEDERAL POLICY AND "SHRINKING CITIES", 2009-2010 (Box R4391)
    - 2009 SRC 162 - PORTLAND PR LIMITED (ENGLAND) - COMMUNICATIONS SUPPORT IN PREPARATION FOR 2009 FORUM FOR CHINA-AFRICA COLLABORATION, 2009-2012 (Box R4391)
    - 2009 SRC 163 - AFRICAN POPULATION AND HEALTH RESEARCH CENTRE (KENYA) - 8th INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON URBAN HEALTH, 2009-2010 (Box R4391)
    - 2009 SRC 164 - HOUSING PARTNERSHIP NETWORK - REGIONAL HOUSING PARTNERSHIPS, 2009-2011 (Box R4391)
    - 2009 SRC 165 - RECONNECTING AMERICA - TRANSIT-ORIENTED DEVELOPMENT TYPOLOGY TOOL, 2009-2011 (Box R4391)
    - 2009 SRC 166 - AFRICAN CENTER FOR ECONOMIC TRANSFORMATION - POST-FOCAC ADVISORY SERVICES TO GOVERNMENT OF LIBERIA, 2009-2011 (Box R4391)
    - 2009 SRC 167 - BOSTON UNIVERSITY - EFFECT OF MAIZE CULTURE ON MALARIA TRANSMISSION IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 2004-2012 (Box R4391)
    - 2009 SRC 168 - NETHOPE - GLOBAL MEMBER SUMMIT, 2008-2010 (Box R4391)
    - 2009 SRC 170 - SOCIETY FOR PARTICIPATORY RESEARCH IN ASIA (INDIA) - PERFORMANCE METRICS DEVELOPMENT, 2009-2011 (Box R4392)
    - 2009 SRC 171 - WORLD TOILET ORGANIZATION LIMITED - STRATEGIC PLANNING AND INFRASTRUCTURE GROWTH, 2009-2010 (Box R4392)
    - 2009 SRC 172 - BRAC UNIVERSITY (BANGLADESH) - IMPROVE QUALITY OF LIVES OF SLUM DWELLERS, 2009-2012 (Box R4392)
    - 2009 SRC 173 - KENYA INFORMATION AND COMMUNICATION TECHNOLOGY BOARD - SHARED SERVICES STRATEGY AND CHANGE MANAGEMENT PLAN FOR KENYAN GOVERNMENT, 2009-2011 (Box R4392)
    - 2009 SRC 175 - UNIVERSITY OF ARIZONA - RESPONSIBLE PROPERTY INVESTMENT MODEL, 2009-2012 (Box R4392)
    - 2009 SRC 176 - INSTITUTE FOR POLICY ALTERNATIVES (GHANA) - PERFORMANCE METRICS DEVELOPMENT IN AFRICA AND ASIA, 2009-2012 (Box R4392)
    - 2009 SRC 177 - POLICYLINK - SUSTAINABLE COMMUNITIES INITIATIVE, 2009-2010 (Box R4392)
    - 2009 SRC 179 - OXFAM AMERICA - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2009-2012 (Box R4392)
    - 2009 SRC 181 - UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA - URBAN WOMEN'S HEALTH eCOMMONS, 2009-2012 (Box R4392)
    - 2009 SRC 182 - NEW YORK ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - SUSTAINABLE CITY FINANCE CONFERENCE, 2009-2010 (Box R4392)
    - 2009 SRC 183 - CHINA MEDICAL BOARD - GLOBAL HEALTH EDUCATION AND RESEARCH INITIATIVES, 2009-2011 (Box R4392)
    - 2009 SRC183 - Health Professionals for a New Century: Transforming Education to Strengthen Health Systems in an Interdependent World - Published Material, 2009-2011; 2014:003:001 (Box R4392)
    - 2009 SRC183 - Health Professionals for a New Century - Published Material, 2009-2011; 2014:003:013 (Box R4392)
    - 2009 SRC 184 - INSTITUTE FOR SUSTAINABLE COMMUNITIES - ROUNDTABLE ON DISASTER RECOVERY, 2009-2010 (Box R4392)
    - 2010 SRC 103 - ENERGY AND RESOURCES INSTITUTE (INDIA) - 2010 DELHI SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT SUMMIT (Box R4409)
    - 2010 SRC 104 - HABITAT FOR HUMANITY INTERNATIONAL - WORLD URBAN FORUM 2010, 2010-2012 (Box R4409)
    - 2010 SRC 105 - URBAN INSTITUTE - EVALUATION OF "HARD TO HOUSE" PROJECT IN CHICAGO, 2007-2010 (Box R4409)
    - 2010 SCR105 - Moving to Opportunity: The Story of an American Experiment of Fight Ghetto Poverty - Published Material, 2007-2010; 2014:003:053 (Box R4409)
    - 2010 SRC 106 - NATIONAL HOUSING LAW PROJECT - "DIALOGUES FOR CHANGE" PROJECT, 2010-2011 (Box R4409)
    - 2010 SRC 107 - CEOs FOR CITIES - "U.S. CAMPAIGN" PROJECT, 2010-2011 (Box R4409)
    - 2010 SRC 108 - NEXT AMERICAN CITY - URBAN LEADERS FELLOWS PROJECT 2010 "OPEN CITIES" CONFERENCE, 2010-2012 (Box R4409)
    - 2010 SRC 109 - PEW CHARITABLE TRUSTS - TRANSPORTATION ASSESSMENT IN THE U.S., 2010-2011 (Box R4409)
    - 2010 SRC 110 - OPERATION USA - WORKSHOP ON THE DESIGN OF REFUGEE CAMPS (Box R4409)
    - 2010 SRC 111 - SANTA FE INSTITUTE - STRUCTURE, DYNAMICS AND ORGANIZATION OF CITIES, AND BELLAGIO CONFERENCE, 2010-2012 (Box R4409)
    - 2010 SRC 112 - LOW INCOME INVESTMENT FUND - TRANSIT-ORIENTED DEVELOPMENT PROJECTS, 2010-2011 (Box R4409)
    - 2010 SRC 113 - BROOKINGS INSTITUTION - PERFORMANCE METRICS FOR WALKABLE URBAN SPACES, 2010-2012 (Box R4409)
    - 2010 SRC 114 - NATIONAL BUILDING MUSEUM - FACILITATE DIALOGUE FOR CREATING SUSTAINABLE CITIES CONFERENCE, 2010-2012 (Box R4410)
    - 2010 SRC114 - Intelligent Cities Photographs June 6, 2011 - Digital, 2010-2012; 2014:003:068 (Box R4410)
    - 2010 SRC114 - Intelligent Cities Ahmed Abukhater, Esri; Sarah Williams - Digital, 2010-2012; 2014:003:067 (Box R4410)
    - 2010 SRC114 - Intelligent Cities Makeshift Metropolis Witold Rybczynski January 10, 2011 - Digital, 2010-2012; 2014:003:066 (Box R4410)
    - 2010 SCR114 - Intelligent Cities - Published Materials, 2010-2012; 2014:003:054 (Box R4410)
    - 2010 SCR114 - Intelligent Cities: Ahmen Abukhater, Esri - Digital, 2010-2012; 2014:003:055 (Box R4410)
    - 2010 SCR114 - Makeshift Metropolis Witold Rybczynsky - Digital, 2010-2012; 2014:003:056 (Box R4410)
    - 2010 SRC 117 - CODE FOR AMERICA LABS - ADOPTION BY MUNICIPAL GOVERNMENTS OF WEB 2.0 APPLICATIONS, 2010-2012 (Box R4410)
    - 2010 SRC 118 - INTERNATIONAL HOUSING COALITION - NEED FOR INCREASED INVESTMENT IN THE DEVELOPING WORLD, 2008-2012 (Box R4410)
    - 2010 SRC 119 - FUND FOR CITIES OF SERVICE - LEADERSHIP GRANTS, 2009-2013 (Box R4410)
    - 2010 SRC 120 - INSTITUTE FOR THE FUTURE - MAP OF FUTURE FORCES, WHITE PAPER ON CITIES AND INFORMATION, 2010-2011 (Box R4410)
    - 2010 SRC 121 - MCKINSEY COMPANY - CITY-RELATED LANDSCAPE ANALYSIS, 2010-2011 (Box R4410)
    - 2010 SRC 122 - MASSACHUSETTS INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY - CONFERENCE ON CITIES AND INFORMATION, 2010-2012 (Box R4410)
    - 2010 SRC 123 - COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY - POLICY IMPLICATIONS OF DATA VISUALIZATION FOR CITIES, 2010-2012 (Box R4410)
    - 2010 SRC 124 - CEOs FOR CITIES, NFP - TECHNOLOGY AND CITIZEN ENGAGEMENT MEETING (Box R4410)
    - 2010 SRC 125 - WORLD WIDE WEB FOUNDATION - VOICE WEB SEARCH PILOT PROJECT, WEB USER RESEARCH (2 FOLDERS), 2010-2012 (Box R4410, Box R4411)
    - 2010 SCR125 - Accelerating Development Using the Web: Empowering Poor and Marginalized Populations - Published Materials, 2010-2012; 2014:003:057 (Box R4411)
    - 2010 SRC 126 - SMART GROWTH AMERICA - NATIONAL VACANT PROPERTIES CAMPAIGN, 2009-2011 (Box R4411)
    - 2010 SCR126 - Restoring Rebuilding Communities: Transforming Vacant Properties in Today's America - Published Material, 2009-2011; 2014:003:058 (Box R4411)
    - 2010 SRC 127 - JUMO INTERNATIONAL - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2010-2012 (Box R4411)
    - 2010 SRC 130 - CEOs FOR CITIES - CONVENE PANEL OF EXPERTS ON ROLES OF CITIES (Box R4411)
    - 2010 SRC 131 - COLD SPRING HARBOR LABORATORY - 75TH ANNIVERSARY OF SYMPOSIUM ON QUANTITATIVE BIOLOGY, 2010-2011 (Box R4411)
    - 2010 SRC 134 - ASHOKA - SUSTAINABLE AND INCLUSIVE HOUSING AND LIVABLE CITIES CHALLENGE, 2010-2011 (Box R4411)
    - 2010 SRC 135 - NEW YORK ACADEMY OF MEDICINE - 9TH INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON URBAN HEALTH, 2010-2011 (Box R4411)
    - 2010 SRC 136 - AMERICAN PLANNING ASSOCIATION - CONFERENCE ON SUSTAINABLE HOUSING IN LATIN AMERICA, 2010-2011 (Box R4411)
    - 2010 SRC 138 - INDIAN SCHOOL OF BUSINESS (INDIA) - URBANIZATION AND AFFORDABLE HOUSING, 2010-2012 (Box R4411)
    - 2010 SRC 139 - MERIDIAN INSTITUTE - SYSTEMS THINKERS CONVENINGS, 2010-2011 (Box R4411)
    - 2010 SRC 140 - WILLIAM J. CLINTON FOUNDATION - 2010 CLINTON GLOBAL INITIATIVE CONFERENCE, 2010-2011 (Box R4411)
    - 2010 SRC 142 - COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY - TROPICAL AGRICULTURE PROGRAM RESEARCH CENTER, 2010-2012 (Box R4411)
    - 2010 SRC 143 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - SOCIAL AND PHYSICAL DETERMINANTS OF URBAN HEALTH IN MUMBAI, INDIA (2 FOLDERS), 2008-2012 (Box R4411, Box R4412)
    - 2010 SRC 146 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA AT BERKELEY - INFRASTRUCTURE DEVELOPMENT PROGRAMS IN KENYA, 2010-2012 (Box R4412)
  - THS, 2007-2013; AC_2014_003_3; 9.2 Cubic Feet 7 record storage boxes
    - 2009 THS 301 - MONITOR COMPANY GROUP - FRANCHISED HEALTH SERVICE PROVIDERS IN INDIA, 2008-2010 (Box R4392)
    - 2009 THS 302 - MANATT, PHELPS PHILLIPS - BC CONFERENCE - CORE eHEALTH TECHNOLOGIES, 2008-2009 (Box R4392)
    - 2009 THS 303 - FREEDOM FROM HUNGER - MICROBUSINESS FOR HEALTH INITIATIVE, GHANA, 2008-2009 (Box R4392)
    - 2009 THS 304 - COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY - MILLENNIUM GLOBAL VILLAGES NETWORK, 2008-2012 (Box R4393)
    - 2009 THS 305 - NEW YORK ACADEMY OF MEDICINE - MINISTERIAL HEALTH LEADERSHIP PROGRAMS BC CONFERENCE, 2008-2010 (Box R4393)
    - 2009 THS 306 - INTERNATIONAL SOCIETY FOR TELEMEDICINE AND EHEALTH (GERMANY) - GLOBAL eHEALTH, 2008-2012 (Box R4393)
    - 2009 THS 307 - DUKE UNIVERSITY - HEALTH SYSTEMS COMPETENCIES AND CURRICULUM INITIATIVE, 2008-2010 (Box R4393)
    - 2009 THS 308 - TRUST FOR INDIGENOUS CULTURE AND HEALTH (KENYA) - TRADITIONAL MEDICINE IN AFRICAN HEALTH SYSTEMS, 2008-2011 (Box R4393)
    - 2009 THS308 - VTM E-Library - Digital, 2008-2011; 2014:003:016 (Box R4393)
    - 2009 THS308 - TICAH Interim VTM Report and Appendices - Digital, 2008-2011; 2014:003:015 (Box R4393)
    - 2009 THS308 - TICAH 2009 THS308 Closeout Rockefeller - Digital, 2008-2011; 2014:003:014 (Box R4393)
    - 2009 THS 309 - HEALTH POLICY INSTITUTE, JAPAN - GLOBAL HEALTH EXPERTS MEETINGS, 2008-2009 (Box R4393)
    - 2009 THS 310 - KAROLINSKA INSTITUTE (SWEDEN) - BEIJING SYMPOSIUM ON PRIVATE SECTOR IN HEALTH, 2008-2010 (Box R4393)
    - 2009 THS310 - The Role of the Private Sector in Health Symposium Report - Published Material, 2008-2010; 2014:003:003 (Box R4393)
    - 2009 THS 311 - BROOKINGS INSTITUTION - HEALTH SYSTEMS IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 2008-2010 (Box R4393)
    - 2009 THS 312 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - MEETING ON HEALTH SYSTEMS RESEARCH AGENDA, 2008-2009 (Box R4393)
    - 2009 THS 313 - MBARARA UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY (UGANDA) - IMPACT OF SCALE-UP OF HIV AIDS PROGRAMS ON HEALTH SYSTEMS IN AFRICA, 2009-2011 (Box R4393)
    - 2009 THS 314 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE FOR DIARRHOEAL DISEASE RESEARCH, BANGLADESH - SHYSTHYA SENA NETWORK, 2008-2012 (Box R4393)
    - 2009 THS314 - Health for the Rural Masses: Insights frok Chakaria - Published Material, 2008-2012; 2014:003:004 (Box R4393)
    - 2009 THS314 - 12th Annual Sciencetific Conference (ASCON XII) Abstracts - Published Material, 2008-2012; 2014:003:002 (Box R4393)
    - 2009 THS 315 - INSTITUTE FOR HEALTH POLICY, SRI LANKA - GOOD HEALTH AT LOW COST, 2008-2010 (Box R4394)
    - 2009 THS 316 - KING'S COLLEGE, CAMBRIDGE (ENGLAND) - ECONOMIC CRISES AND HEALTH IN HISTORICAL PERSPECTIVE, 2009-2010 (Box R4394)
    - 2009 THS 317 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - GLOBAL HEALTH LIBRARY, 2009-2012 (Box R4394)
    - 2009 THS 318 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - HEALTH POLICY ANALYSIS INSTITUTES, 2008-2010 (Box R4394)
    - 2009 THS 319 - MANAGEMENT SCIENCES FOR HEALTH - ACCREDITED DRUD DISPENSING OUTLET ASSOCIATIONS, 2008-2011 (Box R4394)
    - 2009 THS319 - Attaining Universal Health Coverage - A Research Initiative to Support Evidence-Based Advocacy and Policy Making - Published Material, 2008-2011; 2014:003:028 (Box R4394)
    - 2009 THS 320 - AFRICAN HEALTH ECONOMICS AND POLICY ASSOCIATION (UNITED KINGDOM) - PRIORITIES OF HEALTH ECONOMICS IN AFRICA, GHANA 2009, CONFERENCE, 2008-2009 (Box R4394)
    - 2009 THS 322 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - EVALUATION OF SAO PAULO HEALTH INFORMATION SYSTEM, 2009-2010 (Box R4394)
    - 2009 THS 323 - LONDON SCHOOL OF HYGIENE AND TROPICAL MEDICINE, UNIVERSITY OF LONDON (ENGLAND) - ALUMNI DIRECTORY, 2009-2011 (Box R4394)
    - 2009 THS 324 - NATIONAL BUREAU OF ASIAN RESEARCH - PACIFIC HEALTH SUMMIT, 2009-2010 (Box R4394)
    - 2009 THS 326 - GLOBAL FORUM FOR HEALTH RESEARCH (SWITZERLAND) - GLOBAL MINISTERIAL FORUM, 2007-2008 (Box R4394)
    - 2009 THS 327 - GLOBAL HEALTH COUNCIL - 2009 ANNUAL CONFERENCE (Box R4394)
    - 2009 THS327 - Plenary Session 1-5 - Digital, 2014:003:017-2014:003:021 (Box R4394)
    - 2014:003:022 - New Technologies and Proven Strategies Equals Healthy Communities Abstracts - Digital, 2009 (Box R4394)
    - 2014:003:023, 2014:003:024 - New Technologies and Proven Strategies, Equals Healthy Communities Awards Dinner 1 of 2 and 2 of 2 - Digital, 2009 (Box R4394)
    - 2014:003:025 - New Technologies and Proven Strategies Equals Healthy Communities Media Awards Luncheon - Digital, 2009 (Box R4394)
    - New Technologies and Proven Strategies Equals Healthy Communities Special Session 1 and 2 - Digital, 2009; 2014:003:026, 2014:003:027 (Box R4394)
    - 2009 THS 328 - JEMBI HEALTH SYSTEMS (SOUTH AFRICA) - FRAMEWORK STRATEGY FOR INTEGRATED EHEALTH SYSTEMS IN AFRICA, 2009-2012 (Box R4394)
    - 2009 THS 329 - LUIGI BOCCONI UNIVERSITY OF COMMERCE (ITALY) - UNIVERSAL HEALTH COVERAGE TASK FORCE, 2009-2010 (Box R4395)
    - Attaining Universal Health Coverage: A Research Initiative to Support Evidence-based Advocacy and Policy-Making - Published Material, 2009-2010; 2014:003:005 (Box R4395)
    - 2009 THS 330 - UNITED NATIONS FOUNDATION - UN GENERAL ASSEMBLY ON HEALTH SYSTEMS, 2009-2010 (Box R4395)
    - 2009 THS 331 - PROGRAM FOR APPROPRIATE TECHNOLOGY IN HEALTH - ASSESSING PROSPECTS FOR UNIVERSAL HEALTH COVERAGE, 2009-2011 (Box R4395)
    - 2009 THS 332 - HELENE DE BEIR FOUNDATION (BELGIUM) - GLOBAL HEALTH RIGHTS CONFERENCE, 2009-2010 (Box R4395)
    - 2009 THS 333 - EMORY UNIVERSITY - SMALLPOX ERADICATION COMMEMORATION 2010, 2009-2011 (Box R4395)
    - 2009 THS 334 - INTERNATIONAL HEALTH ECONOMICS ASSOCIATION - 7th WORLD CONGRESS ON HEALTH ECONOMICS. BEIJING, CHINA, 2009-2012 (Box R4395)
    - 2009 THS 336 - MAHIDOL UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - PRINCE MAHIDOL AWARD CONFERENCES 2010-2012, 2009-2012 (Box R4395)
    - 2009 THS336 - The Second Global Forum on Human Resources for Health Prince Mahidol Award Conference 2011 - Published Material, 2009-2012; 2014:003:026 (Box R4395)
    - 2009 THS336 - Global Health Information Forum 2010 - Published Material, 2009-2012; 2014:003:007 (Box R4395)
    - 2009 THS336 - Global Health Information Forum 2010 - Digital, 2009-2012; 2014:003:029 (Box R4395)
    - 2009 THS 340 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA, SAN FRANCISCO - HEALTH SYSTEMS INITIATIVE, 2009-2012 (Box R4395)
    - 2009 THS 341 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - GLOBAL HEALTH SYSTEMS, eHEALTH AND UNIVERSAL HEALTH COVERAGE, 2009-2013 (Box R4396)
    - 2009 THS 341 - Health Systems Financing: the Path to Universal Coverage - Publihsed Material, 2009-2013; 2014:003:008 (Box R4396)
    - 2009 THS 342 - KIWANJA FOUNDATION (UNITED KINGDOM) - FRONTLINESMS, MOBILE HEALTH PILOT, 2009-2011 (Box R4396)
    - 2009 THS 343 - D-TREE Inc. - JavaROSA PLATFORM IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 2009-2010 (Box R4396)
    - 2009 THS 344 - CENTRE FOR HEALTH AND SOCIAL SERVICES (GHANA) - STRENGTHEN NATIONAL HEALTH SYSTEMS, 2009-2013 (Box R4396)